this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in today's tutorial I'll be
在今天的教程中，我将
demonstrating how you can create this
演示如何创建
vintage style text poster using Inkscape
使用Inkscape的复古风格文本海报
and if you'd like to learn more about
如果你想了解更多关于
helping state berks be sure to check out
帮助州立大学确保结账
the Inkscape master class which is a
Inkscape主类，它是
collection of over 50 videos where i go
收集了50多个我去过的地方的视频
over all of the major tools and features
所有主要工具和功能
in Inkscape and i explain what they are
在Inkscape中，我解释了它们是什么
and demonstrate how they work I'll put a
并演示它们是如何工作的，我会把一个
link in the description of the video if
视频描述中的链接，如果
you want to check that out so I'm gonna
你想检查一下吗？所以我要
go ahead and get started here in
去吧，在这里开始
Inkscape I'm gonna open up a blank
Inkscape我要打开一片空白
canvas as you can see here and I just
就像你在这里看到的画布，我只是
want to make sure that we're all working
想要确保我们都在工作
with a similar view before we get
有类似的观点，在我们得到
started so I'm just gonna come up here
开始了，所以我要到这里来
to where it says view make sure you have
到它说的地方，查看，确保你有
custom selected and then we'll go to
自定义选择，然后我们将转到
zoom we're going to zoom in at 1 to 1
我们将以1比1的比例放大
and then I'll open up the align and
然后我会打开Align和
distribute menu with this button over
将此按钮放在上方的分发菜单
here and then I will open up the Edit
在这里，我将打开编辑
objects colors gradients and Stroke menu
对象、颜色、渐变和笔触菜单
with this button right here and where it
用这个按钮就在这里，在哪里
says online and distribute you're gonna
在网上说并分发你将
want to make sure you have last selected
想要确保您上次选择了
chosen where it says relative too and
选择了它说的也是相对的地方
once we've done that we're good to get
一旦我们做到这一点，我们就可以
started so the first thing we're going
所以我们要做的第一件事就是
to create is the actual text so I'm
创建的是实际的文本，所以我
gonna grab the text tool over here and
我要把文本工具拿过来，然后
I'm gonna click on the canvas I'm gonna
我要点击画布，我要
use all caps for weather right now I'm
使用所有的大写字母表示天气，现在我是
going to create each text item on its
将在其
own line so I'm gonna write how for the
我自己的台词，所以我要为
first line second line to create and for
要创建的第一行和第二行
this third line vintage just like I had
这三条线的年份和我以前一样
in the thumbnail of the video how to
在视频的缩略图中如何
create vidiq text and posters each on
分别创建VidIQ文本和海报
its own line and what I'll do now is let
它自己的线路，我现在要做的是让
me grab the Select tool I want to take
我抓起我想要使用的选择工具
this text right here this middle word
这篇文章就在这里这个中间的词
vintage if you saw in the thumbnail of
如果你在缩略图中看到
the design I had that word over I had it
我有这个词的设计我已经有了
placed on top of like a banner so I want
放在像横幅一样的顶部，所以我想
to make sure I use a different font for
要确保我使用不同的字体
this for this word right here I'm gonna
为了这个词，我要在这里
open up the text editor I'm gonna click
打开文本编辑器，我要点击
on that text and hold ctrl shift T to
在该文本上并按住Ctrl Shift T以
open up the text editor or you just
打开文本编辑器，否则您只需
click on this T icon up here I like to
点击这里的这个T图标我喜欢
use control shift T cuz it's easier and
使用Ctrl Shift T，因为它更容易和
the font I'm going to use is called Z a
我要使用的字体名为Za
B is a zaba Tanna poster I'm gonna go
B是Zaba Tanna的海报，我要去
with that I'll have a link in the
有了这个，我就可以在
description to a poster I have all of
对一张我所有的海报的描述
the fonts
字体
and textures I'm gonna be using in this
以及我将在这部电影中使用的纹理
tutorial you don't necessarily have to
教程您并不一定要
use these fonts that I'm using you can
使用我正在使用的这些字体，您可以使用
use whatever fonts you'd like but if you
使用您喜欢的任何字体，但如果您
really want to get that vintage look
我真的很想要那种复古的造型
that I have in the a thumbnail the video
我在缩略图里有一段视频
I'd recommend downloading and installing
我建议下载并安装
these fonts so I'm going to apply that I
这些字体，所以我将应用我的
want to make that a little bigger by
想把它做得更大一点吗
holding ctrl and shift and clicking and
按住Ctrl和Shift并单击和
dragging to scale that up and for these
拖动以向上扩展，并针对这些
text items over here
文本项目在这里
I want the font I'm going to use for
我想要我要用的字体
that is ctrl shift T I'm going to use
这是Ctrl Shift T，我将使用
League gothic there we go of me use the
哥特式联盟，我们去那里，用我的
normal regular size apply that let me
正常的正常尺寸，让我
make that a little bigger ctrl shift and
把它调大一点，然后按下ctrl键
scale that up and I just want to put
把它放大，我只想把它
everything near each other over here let
这里距离彼此很近的一切都让
me click and drag over all of these and
我点击并拖动所有这些，然后
in the align distribute menu I'm going
在对齐分布菜单中，我要
to Center them on the vertical axis and
使它们在垂直轴上居中，并
then I'll come down here to distribute
那我就下来这里分发
and I'm going to click on make vertical
然后我将点击垂直设置
gaps between objects equal so let me
物体之间的间距相等，所以让我
click off of that to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
what I want to do now is make each of
我现在想做的是让每个人
these objects the same width
这些对象具有相同的宽度
except for this middle text right here
除了这段中间的文字
so let me click on this word right here
所以让我在这里点击这个词
I'm going to turn on this lock icon
我要打开这个锁图标
where it says when lock changed both the
其中说明了锁定何时更改了
width and the height by the same
宽度和高度相同
proportion turn that on I'm gonna right
按比例打开，我要向右转
click that and go to copy and then when
单击该选项并转到复制，然后在
I click on this top word up here and go
我在这里点击这个最热门的词，然后开始
to edit paste size paste width and it's
编辑粘贴大小粘贴宽度和它的
gonna make it the same width as the next
我会让它和下一个一样宽
item I'll come down here and do the same
我会到这里来做同样的事情
thing edit paste size paste width we're
东西编辑粘贴大小粘贴宽度我们正在
not going to do this with this middle
我不会用这个中间人做这个
word here because this word needs to be
因为这个词需要是
a little bigger than the others because
比其他的大一点，因为
this is gonna go on a banner and it'll
这将出现在横幅上，它将
do the same thing down here edit paste
在这里执行相同的操作编辑粘贴
size paste with and what I will do now
粘贴大小和我现在要做的事情
is I want to put little lines between
我想在两条线之间加点线
these two text items right here so I'm
这两个文本项就在这里，所以我
gonna grab the squares and rectangles
我要抓住正方形和长方形
tool and I'll just click and drag to
工具，我只需点击并拖动到
create a little rectangle in there let
在那里创建一个小矩形，让
me get rid of that stroke by holding
我拿着它就能摆脱那次中风
shift and clicking the X I want to make
按住Shift键并单击要创建的X
that black I grab the Select tool bring
我抓起选择工具带来的那块黑色
that down a little bit these are just
再往下一点，这些只是
meant to be little access little accent
意思是很难接近的口音
pieces they don't have to you don't have
他们不需要的东西你也没有
to necessarily use these but I think
有必要使用这些，但我认为
they make the design just come together
他们把设计拼凑在一起
a little more and again I want to make
更多一点，我想一次又一次地
these I want to make these the same
我想把这些都做成一样的
width so I'll go to edit
宽度，因此我将转到编辑
paste size paste width there we go now
粘贴大小粘贴宽度现在开始
let me right click that little duplicate
让我用鼠标右键点击那个小副本
bring this one down here there we go let
把这个拿下来，我们走吧，让我们
me bring these all a little closer now
我现在把这些都拉近一点
in fact I want to take this middle text
事实上，我想用这个中间文本
right here and make that even bigger
就在这里，让它变得更大
right about there
就在那里
bring these a little closer now I'm
把这些拿近一点，现在我
going to click and drag over all of
要单击并拖动所有
these I'm gonna do the same thing again
这些我会再次做同样的事情
the same thing again I'm gonna Center
再说一次，我要把中心放在
them on the vertical axis and then
它们在垂直轴上，然后
distribute make vertical gaps between
分布在以下位置之间形成垂直间隙
objects in equal like that okay now I'm
像这样平等的物体好的，现在我
going to click off of that to deselect
要单击该选项以取消选择
everything now what I'm gonna do is
现在我要做的一切就是
we're gonna work on creating a banner
我们将致力于制作一个横幅
for this word vintage right here so let
为了这个词，就在这里，所以让我们
me take these objects right here and
我把这些东西放在这里
just hold ctrl and just move them out of
只需按住Ctrl键并将它们移出
the way a little bit and I'll take these
往前走一点，我要这些。
objects and do the same thing hold ctrl
对象并执行相同的操作，请按住Ctrl键
move it up out of the way and now I'm
把它挪开，现在我要
gonna grab the squares and rectangles
我要抓住正方形和长方形
tool well you know what first what I
好的，你知道吗，我首先要做的是
want to do is let me go back to the
想要做的就是让我回到
Select tool let me click on this text
选择工具让我点击此文本
right here and make this white then I'll
就在这里，把这个弄白，然后我就
grab the squares and rectangles tool and
抓起正方形和矩形工具并
I'm gonna create a rectangle going over
我要创建一个长方形
the text right there I'm gonna make that
就在那里的文字，我要把它
black grab the Select tool I'm gonna
黑色抓取选择工具我要
send that to the bottom by clicking the
通过单击下面的
button that says lower selection to the
按钮，该按钮表示较低的选择范围
bottom or what I like to do is just
或者我喜欢做的就是
press end on the keyboard at the end key
在键盘上的End键上按End键
and it sends it to the bottom that's
它把它送到底部，那就是
good let me just size that up a little
好的，让我稍微估计一下。
better we want a little bit of padding
更好的是，我们需要一点填充物
around the edges not too much though and
在边缘周围不要太多，而且
then I'll hold shift and click on the
然后按住Shift键并单击
word and just make sure I have it
一句话，只要确保我有
centered up on the vertical and
在垂直方向居中，
horizontal axis let me click on that
横轴，让我点击一下
click off of it to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
now I'll take just this object right
现在我要把这个物体拿对了
here just this rectangle I'll get a path
这里就是这个长方形，我会找到一条路径
object to path and then I'm gonna
反对PATH然后我会
right-click it and go to duplicate and
右键单击它，然后转到复制和
I'm gonna make this red and I'm gonna
我要把它染成红色，我要
give this a red stroke by holding shift
通过按住Shift键为其添加红色笔划
and clicking on the color red and then I
然后点击红色，然后我
want to send that to the bottom by
想把它送到底部吗？
pressing end on the keyboard and the red
按键盘上的End键和红色键
stroke I want to make that a little
中风，我想做得更好一点。
thicker I'm gonna come up here to the
再厚一点，我要到这里来
stroke style tab but I'm gonna increase
笔划样式选项卡，但我将增加
the size of that a little bit maybe a
它的大小可能有一点
little bit more there we go that's
我们再往前走一点，那就是
that's a good that's a good thickness
那很好，厚度很好。
right there now what I want to do is
现在我想做的是
convert this to a path so I'll go to
将其转换为路径，这样我将转到
path stroke the path
路径描边路径
and then paths break apart and then
然后小路分开，然后
paths Union and the whole point of that
路径并集以及它的全部意义
was to end up with the rectangle just
就是最终得到一个长方形
like this black one here only slightly
就像这件黑色的，只是稍微有点
thicker on all on both dimensions right
在两个维度上都更厚右
there now what I want to do is take this
现在我想做的就是拿着这个
black rectangle and duplicate that I'm
黑色矩形和复制品，我是
gonna click on it then press control D
我要点击它，然后按Ctrl D
on the keyboard I'm trying to take this
在键盘上，我正试着拿着这个
and move this down to the left over here
把这个向下移到这里的左边
like that and I'm gonna send that to the
像这样，我会把它寄给
bottom by pressing end on the keyboard
按键盘上的End键向下
let me move this down here like this I'm
让我把这个像这样搬下来，我要
gonna grab the nodes tool click and drag
要抓取结点工具，请单击并拖动
over these two these two nodes to the
通过这两个节点将这两个节点连接到
right right here hold ctrl and just
就在这里，按住Ctrl键，然后
click and drag these over to the left
单击并将其拖到左侧
like that this is gonna be like the tail
就像这样，这就像尾巴
kind of like the tail of the ribbon
有点像丝带的尾巴
right about there is good now I'm gonna
好了，现在我要去
click and drag over those nodes right
在这些节点上单击并向右拖动
there and I want to insert a new node in
我想在其中插入一个新节点
the middle so we'll come up here to the
中间，所以我们要到这里来
very top left where it says insert new
在最左上角的位置显示插入新项
nodes into selected segments click on
将节点添加到选定线段中，单击
that and then I want to click on just
然后我想点击
that new node right there and hold ctrl
该新节点就在那里，然后按住Ctrl键
and just move this over to the right to
把这个移到右边就可以了
give it kind of like a little bit of a
让它看起来有点像
fish tail for the ends there may be a
鱼尾巴的末端可能有一个
little less that's good right there now
稍微少一点，现在就很好
let me grab the Select tool again let me
让我再次抓起选择工具让我
duplicate that by hitting ctrl D on the
通过按Ctrl D键复制此操作
keyboard and I will flip that
键盘和我将翻转它
horizontally and bring this over here to
水平方向，把这个拿到这里
the top right and I want to send this to
右上角，我想把这个发送到
the bottom as well I'm gonna press end
底部也一样，我要按End键
on the keyboard I want to bring this
在键盘上，我想把这个
right about here and then I'll hold
就在这里，然后我就会等着
shift and click on the other one so we
按住Shift键并单击另一个键，这样我们
have both of these little ribbon tails
这两条小丝带尾巴都有
selected and I'll go to path Union and
选中后，我将转到Path Union，然后
then I'll hold shift and click on this
然后按住Shift键并单击此按钮
red rectangle right here and Center it
红色矩形就在这里并居中
up on the vertical and horizontal axis
在垂直轴和水平轴上向上
like that and then I'll go to path
就像那样，然后我会去小路
difference and there you have our ribbon
不同之处，这就是我们的丝带
so let me take this text these text
所以让我把这段文字，这些文字
objects right here and just hold ctrl
对象就在这里并按住Ctrl键
and move them up a little bit and I'll
把它们往上移一点，我就会
do the same thing with these I'll click
对这些做同样的事情，我会点击
and drag over those hold ctrl move these
然后将鼠标拖到这些位置上，按住Ctrl键移动这些
down a little bit like that and that's
像这样往下一点，那就是
what I'm looking for right there now
我现在正在寻找的就是
what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna click and
我要做的是点击并点击
drag over everything I'm gonna group
拖过我要分组的所有东西
them together by clicking the button up
通过向上单击按钮将它们放在一起
here that says group selected objects or
此处表示对选定对象进行分组或
you could just press ctrl G because I
你只要按下Ctrl G就行了，因为我
like to do and
喜欢做和做
I'm going to share it a little bit so
我要分享一点，所以
I'm gonna click on this object again if
如果出现以下情况，我将再次单击此对象
you notice here when you have it
当你拥有它的时候，你会注意到这里
selected you have these arrows right
选中后，这些箭头就会显示正确
here these are the scaling handles they
这里是它们的缩放手柄
allow you to scale an object if I click
如果我单击，则允许您缩放对象
on the object its gonna give us the
在这个物体上它会给我们
rotation and the shearing handles which
旋转和剪切手柄
will allow us to either rotate or shear
将允许我们旋转或剪切
the object I want this shearing handle
我想要这个剪刀把手
over here to the right I'm just gonna
在这里，在右边，我只是要
click and drag that up a little bit
单击并将其向上拖动一点
maybe about that much right there that's
也许就在那里，大概有那么多
pretty good and now it's time to create
很好，现在是时候创造
kind of like a frame or a border going
有点像一个边框或边框
around the words here so let me grab the
围绕着这里的单词，让我抓住
squares and rectangles tool again I'm
又是正方形和长方形工具，我是
gonna click and drag to create a
将单击并拖动以创建一个
rectangle going over all of those words
矩形复习所有这些单词
I want to make this I want to give this
我想做这个，我想送这个
a black outline so I'm gonna hold shift
黑色的轮廓，所以我要按住Shift
and click on the color black and I want
然后点击黑色，我想
it to have no fill so I'm gonna click on
没有填充物，所以我要点击
this red X to get rid of a fill color
这个红色的X去掉了填充颜色
and I want to make that border a little
我想把这个边框做得有点
thinner I don't want to be that thick
我不想变得那么胖
I'm gonna try maybe eight eight pixels
我可能会尝试8个8像素
that looks pretty good okay so let me go
看起来很不错，好的，让我走吧
back to the Select tool let me convert
返回到选择工具，让我转换
that to a path by going to path object
通过转到路径对象将其转换为路径
to path and then I want to hold shift
到PATH然后我想按住Shift
and click on the text objects just to
然后点击文本对象，只是为了
make sure we have it centered up on this
确保我们把它集中在这个上面
horizontal and vertical axis like that
像这样的水平轴和垂直轴
now let me click off of that to deselect
现在，让我单击该选项以取消选择
everything and click on just this
所有内容，然后只点击这个
rectangle right here I'm gonna go back
长方形就在这里，我要回去
to the nodes tool the edit pads by nodes
到结点工具按结点编辑焊盘
click and drag over these top two nodes
在这两个顶部节点上单击并拖动
insert a new node in there and do the
在其中插入一个新节点，然后执行
same thing down here take those two
同样的事情发生在这里，把那两个人带走
nodes and put a new one in there now
节点，然后将一个新节点放入其中
what I want to do is grab just those two
我想做的就是抓住这两个人
nodes right there click and drag over
就在那里的节点上单击并拖动
both of those and up here in the tool
这两个和工具上的这里
settings you're gonna see show
你将会看到的场景
transformation handles for selected
所选对象的变换句柄
nodes if I turn that on it's going to
节点如果我打开它，它将会
give us scaling handles for the nodes
为我们提供节点的缩放句柄
that we have selected which is going to
我们已经选择了哪一个将
be useful here which is what I want I'm
在这里做个有用的人这就是我想要的
gonna hold ctrl and shift and I'm gonna
按住Ctrl键和Shift键，然后我要
grab the scaling handle up here and you
抓住这里的刻度手柄，你就可以
just pull this out a little bit if you
把这个拉出来一点，如果你
notice here we're giving the top and the
请注意，我们在这里给出了顶部和
bottom a little bit of a tip like that
给一点小费，就像这样
now I'm going to turn off the scaling
现在我要关闭缩放功能
handles show transformation handles for
句柄显示以下对象的变换句柄
selective nodes turn that back off so it
选择性节点会将其重新关闭，以便它
doesn't get in your way the next time
下一次不会妨碍你
you go to use the nodes tool later on
稍后您将使用结点工具
I'm gonna grab the select tool okay that
我去拿选择工具，好的
right there is looking pretty good
就在那里，看起来相当不错
that's about what I'm looking for now
这就是我现在要找的东西
what I want to do is put another border
我想要做的是再加上一条边界
around
在附近
outside edge of this border only
仅此边框的外缘
slightly thinner so what I'm gonna do is
稍微瘦了一点，所以我要做的是
I'm gonna duplicate this I'm going to
我要复制这个，我要
press control D on the keyboard and I'm
按下键盘上的Ctrl D键，我就
gonna fill this with white and I'm gonna
我要把这个装满白色，我要
give this a white outline by holding
给它一个白色的轮廓，拿着
shift and clicking the the color of
按住Shift键并单击
white and for the width I'll make this
白色的，至于宽度，我会做这个
larger I'm gonna go with maybe let's say
我要更大的，也许我会说
twelve see how that looks
12个人看看那是什么样子
and I want to send this to the bottom
我想把这个送到最下面
lower select objects to the bottom
将选择的对象放到底部
that's going to act this white border is
这个白色边框就是
gonna act as a buffer between the large
将会在大的
black border and the smaller black
黑色边框和较小的黑色
border so let me duplicate that again
边框，让我再重复一遍
control D and I'll make this one black
Ctrl D和我会把这个设为黑色
and give it a black stroke by holding
并通过按住它来给它黑色的笔划
shift and clicking on black and I'll
按住Shift键并单击黑色，我将
send that to the bottom as well and I'm
把它也送到底部，我就会
gonna want to make this one a little
我想把这件事做得稍微
better a little bigger I'm gonna try 20
最好再大一点，我要试20个
okay so that's not quite what I'm
好的，所以这不是我想要的
looking for let me zoom in a little bit
寻找让我放大一点的
you could zoom in and out by holding
您可以通过按住鼠标左键进行放大和缩小
ctrl and rolling up the mouse wheel I'm
按住Ctrl键并卷起鼠标滚轮
gonna take this white one right here I
我要买这个白色的，就在这里
want this border this gap between the
想要这个边界，这个缝隙，
two borders to be bigger so I'm gonna
两个更大的边界，所以我要
make this one maybe 16 maybe 15 and then
把这张做成16张，15张，然后
I'll take the other at the outer black
我要在外面的黑道上坐另一辆
border over here and I'll make that I'm
边界在这里，我会让我成为
gonna make this a little bigger than 25
会让这件事比25件稍微大一点
looks a little too big
看起来有点太大了
let me try 22 a little bigger I'm just
让我试一下22号，我只是
going to manually adjust that until it
我要手动调整，直到它
looks about right
看起来差不多了
that right there is about what I'm
这就是关于我是什么
looking for I think that looks pretty
寻找我认为那看起来很漂亮
good so now I can click off of
很好，现在我可以点击
everything I want to zoom in and take
所有我想要放大和拍摄的东西
just this outer border right here I want
就是这个外框，就在这里，我想
to go to path stroke to path path break
转到路径笔划到路径分隔符
apart path Union and I'm gonna do the
分开的路径联盟和我要做的是
same thing to the inner white border
内侧白色边框也是如此
right there path stroke the path path
就在那里路径笔划路径路径
break apart path Union and then hold
拆分路径并集，然后按住
shift and click on the outer black
按住Shift键并单击外部黑色
border so that we have both the white
边框，这样我们既有白色的
and the black borders selected and go to
并选择黑色边框，然后转到
path difference now I'm going to click
路径差异现在我要点击
on the large black border and here the
在巨大的黑色边框上，在这里
original one and I'm going to convert
原来的那个，我要改装成
that to a path as well by going to path
这也是通过转到路径来实现的
stroke the path and then finally I'm
抚摸这条小路，然后我终于
going to hold shift I'm gonna click on
按住Shift键，然后点击
the other border so we have both of
另一个边界，所以我们有两个
these borders selected and go to path
选中这些边框并转到路径
Union now let me press one on the
工会现在让我按一下
keyboard to zoom back out to 100% let me
键盘缩小到100%让我
click off it to deselect everything it's
单击它以取消选择它所属的所有内容
looking pretty good now it's gonna make
现在看起来很不错，它会让
a few minor edits and we'll be all
做一些小的修改，我们就可以
finished so let me click on the text
完成了，让我点击文本
objects in here and let me ungroup them
对象放在这里，让我解开它们
by clicking the button that says ungroup
通过单击表示解组的按钮
selected objects or you can press ctrl
选定的对象，也可以按Ctrl键
shift G like that and what I will do now
像这样换G，我现在要做什么
is I want to take this border right here
我想把这条边境线拿到这里
I mean that this border this black
我的意思是这个边界是这个黑色的
rectangle right here I want to duplicate
矩形就在这里，我想复制
that by pressing control D and I want to
通过按下Control D和我想要的
make that red and I want to bring the
把它改成红色，我想带上
opacity down in half roughly in half
不透明度减半，大约减半
what I want to do is create a gap in
我想要做的是在
these borders right here between the
这些边界就在这里
ribbon and the borders so I'm gonna use
丝带和边框，所以我要用
this red rectangle as a reference point
此红色矩形作为参照点
for that so let me grab the nodes tool
为此，让我拿起结点工具
again I'm gonna clicking drag over this
我再一次将鼠标拖到这上面
top node then I'll hold your shift click
顶部节点，然后我将按住您的Shift单击
and drag over this node over here and
将此节点拖到此处，然后
I'm gonna hold ctrl and click and drag
我要按住Ctrl键并单击并拖动
that up that's what about there that
往上，就是那个，那个怎么样？
looks good
看上去不错
I'll do the same thing down here
我也会在这里做同样的事情
clicking drag over this node hold shift
在此节点上单击拖动并按住Shift键
click and drag over that node and then
在该节点上单击并拖动，然后
hold control and move this one down to
按住Ctrl键并将此键向下移动到
about there so that is sticking out just
关于那里，所以这是突出的
a little bit further than the black
比黑色稍微远一点
ribbon beneath it then I'll grab the
在它下面的丝带，然后我会抓住
Select tool hold shift click on your
选择工具按住Shift键单击您的
border right there and go to path
边框就在那里，然后转到Path
difference and that right there was the
不同之处就在那里
point of that I wanted to create that
重点是我想要创造一个
gap between the poor and the ribbon
贫富差距和贫富差距
right there so the next step is I want
就在那里，所以下一步我想
to add a little bit of a little bit of
要添加一点一点的
an accent piece right here in the
一首重音乐曲就在这里
corners of the top and the bottom so to
顶部和底部的角，以便
do that first what I want to do is
首先，我想做的是
enable snapping I'm gonna come up here
启用捕捉，我要到这里来
to where it says enable snapping turn
转到它显示启用捕捉转弯的位置
that on and we're gonna want to make
我们要做的就是
sure we have this one selected it says
当然，我们已经选好了，上面写着
snap custom nodes and this was well snap
捕捉自定义节点，这是一次很好的捕捉
snaps smooth nodes and I'm going to take
捕捉平滑节点，我将使用
this border right here and I'm gonna
这条边界就在这里，我要
duplicate that by hitting ctrl D on the
通过按Ctrl D键复制此操作
keyboard and I'm gonna make this red and
键盘和我要把它变成红色和
I'm gonna bring the opacity down in half
我要把不透明度降低一半
now it's gonna click and drag and move
现在它会点击、拖拽和移动
this up I'm gonna snap this piece I'm
我要拍下这张照片，我要
gonna snap the bottom corner into the
我要把底角扣进
top corner of the original one right
原图右上角
there and I want to take this red area
在那里，我想要这个红色的区域
what that's sticking out I want to use
我想用它突出的是什么
that as the accent piece so let me grab
作为重音部分，让我抓起
the Bezier pen which is over here or you
贝塞尔钢笔是在这里还是你
could press B on the keyboard
可以按键盘上的B键
and I'm gonna start a line going right
我要开始一条正确的路线
here in the middle of the black border
在这里，在黑色边界的中央
come over here through here like this
像这样从这里走过来
oops we go through here then here then
哦，我们先从这里走，然后再到这里
back to the starting point
回到起点
grab the Select tool hold shift on the
按住按住Shift键的选择工具
keyboard and click on the red object and
键盘并单击红色对象，然后
go to the path intersection and that's
走到小路交叉口，那就是
what I'm looking for right there now I
我现在正在寻找的就是我
want to duplicate that by hitting ctrl D
我想通过按Ctrl D来复制它
I want to flip that vertically and I
我想垂直翻转它，然后我
want to click and drag this down here
我想点击并将其拖到这里
and then snap this onto there like that
然后像这样把这个扣在那里
now let me zoom out a little bit again
现在让我再缩小一点
I'm holding ctrl and rolling down the
我按住Ctrl键并滚动
mouse wheel to zoom I'm gonna hold your
鼠标滚轮来缩放我要拿着你的
shift click on that red object so we
按住Shift键点击红色对象，以便我们
have both red objects selected and then
选择两个红色对象，然后
I'm gonna hold shift and click on them
我要按住Shift键并单击它们
on the border and go to path Union and
在边界上，然后去Path Union和
now I'll go to path break apart so that
现在我要去分道扬镳，这样
everything is an individual piece now
现在一切都是一件独立的作品
and the whole point of that as you can
而你所能做的就是
see here is to create this little indent
这里看到的是创建这个小缩进
just a nice little accent piece for the
只是一个很好的小口音为
design so the final step I would say
所以我要说的是设计最后一步
would be to add the texture but first I
是为了增加质感，但首先我
want to add a little bit of color so let
想要增加一点颜色，所以让我们
me uh first let me click and drag over
我，嗯，首先让我点击并拖动到
everything and go to path object to path
所有内容并转到路径对象到路径
and that's going to take that text and
这将会把这段文字
change it from text objects to actual
将其从文本对象更改为实际
pads that we can work with now I want to
我们现在可以使用的垫子，我想
click off of it to deselect I want to
单击它以取消选择我想要
take just this word vintage right here I
就拿这个词来说吧，复古
want to ungroup it unify it together by
想要解开它，通过以下方式将其统一在一起
going to path Union and then hold shift
转到Path Union，然后按住Shift键
and click on the banner underneath it
然后点击它下面的横幅
and go to path difference and what that
然后转到路径差之类的地方
did was it pretty much just used the
是不是差不多就是用了
text as a reference to punch negative
文本作为冲压负片的参考
space punch a hole through the ribbon
空格键在色带上打孔
there so that I can change the colors
这样我就可以换颜色了
and do whatever I want to it and as you
做任何我想做的事，就像你
can see it's kind of like a negative
我可以看到这就像是一种负片
space between there in those words so
在这些词中有空格所以
now that I've done that I want to give
现在我已经做到了，我想给你
this thing some color I'm gonna click
我要点击这件东西的颜色
and drag over all of it I'm gonna give
然后拖着我要给你的一切
this like a little royal blue or like a
这看起来像是一点皇家蓝或者像是
dark navy blue something like that
深色海军蓝之类的
that's pretty good I want to take this
太好了，我想要这个。
word I actually want to take this piece
听说我真的想拍这首曲子
right here and make this a shade of gold
就在这里，把这个变成金色
obviously you can color this and however
显然，你可以给这个上色，但是
you'd like you don't have to use the
您会希望您不必使用
colors I'm using here
我在这里使用的颜色
I'm gonna go the fill tab up here under
我要去填满标签，在这下面
the HSL tab I'm gonna take the
HSL标签，我将使用
saturation just bring that down a little
饱和度只需将其降低一点
bit you bring this up a little bit as
你把这件事提得有点像
well I want to do the same thing I want
我想做我想做的事
to hold shift and click on both the word
按住Shift键并同时单击该单词
text and this accent piece right here I
文本和这里的重音部分是我
want to grab the dropper tool and make
想要抓起滴管工具并使
that the same color as this there we go
和这个一样的颜色，我们走吧
and I want to take let me grab the nodes
我想拿来，让我抓住节点
tool I'm gonna click on just the word
工具，我将只点击这个词
create here and click on that hold shift
在此处创建并单击按住Shift键
click on that each letter individually
逐个点击每个字母
so that we have them all selected go
这样我们就把它们都选好了
back to the Select tool and then grab
返回到选择工具，然后抓取
the dropper and make that the same color
滴管，并使其颜色相同
right there and then finally I want to
就在那里，然后最后我想要
take the outer border right here and I
把外边界拿到这里，然后我
want to make that the same color as the
我想让它的颜色与
gold so let me select those both grab
黄金，所以让我来选两个都抓的
the dropper over here or you can press D
滴管放在这里，你也可以按D键
on the keyboard that's also another way
在键盘上，这也是另一种方式
to grab it grab the Select tool press 1
要抓取它，抓取选择工具按1
on the keyboard to zoom back out to 100%
在键盘上缩小到100%
and what I'm going to do now is just
我现在要做的就是
click and drag over all of this and
点击并拖动所有这些内容，然后
group this together ctrl G to group it
将其组合在一起按Ctrl G将其分组
together let me turn off the snapping
一起让我关掉抓拍
for now because that's just gonna get in
就目前而言，因为那只会进入
our way the final step is to add a
我们的方法最后一步是添加一个
little bit of a texture on here to make
在这里要做一点纹理
it look worn aged and again I'll have a
它看起来很旧了，我要再来一次
link in the description of the video to
视频描述中的链接
a to a page with all of the resources
A到包含所有资源的页面
including this texture what I'm going to
包括这个质地，我要做的
do is once you have the texture hoping
一旦你有了质感，你就会希望
I'm gonna bring my folder over here just
我要把我的文件夹拿过来
so you can see I have my folder over
所以你可以看到我把文件夹放在那里
here I'm gonna take the I'm gonna take
在这里我要拿着我要拿的
the texture grunge texture dot PNG and
纹理垃圾纹理网点PNG和
just click and drag it into Inkscape
只需点击并将其拖动到Inkscape
like that and just leave this little
就像这样，只留下这一点
window that pops up just leave all the
弹出的窗口只留下所有
defaults there go ahead and click OK and
此处的默认设置请继续，然后单击确定
there you have the texture let me zoom
这就是纹理，让我来放大
out a little bit so you can see this let
稍微向外一点，这样你就可以看到这个字母
me bring the opacity of that down
我把它的不透明性降下来
roughly in half so we can see what's on
大致对半，这样我们就可以看到正在上映的是什么
there as well so what I want to do is
所以我想要做的是
place this texture over the image right
将此纹理放置在图像的右侧
here I'm gonna hold ctrl + shift and
在这里，我将按住Ctrl+Shift并
scale this down a little bit now if you
现在稍微缩小一下，如果你
notice where the black areas of the
请注意，其中的黑色区域
textures are like this is the black
纹理是这样的，这是黑色
scratch marks when I apply this texture
当我应用此纹理时会有划痕
to this design all of those black
对于这个设计，所有那些黑色的
scratches are gonna represent negative
划痕代表阴性
space in the design so all of those
设计中的空间，所以所有这些
black scratches are going to become
黑色的划痕将会成为
white or negative space within that
其中的空白或负数
design you'll see what I mean when I
你会明白我的意思，当我
apply the
应用
texture so I'm telling you that so you
质地，所以我告诉你，所以你
can you could try to figure out where
你能不能试着找出
exactly you want the texture to be
就是你想要的纹理
because like if you take this area right
因为如果你把这一区域处理好
here which is all black and place it
在这里，全部是黑色的，把它放在
over here it's gonna punch out a big
在这里，它会冲出一个很大的
area of the design that's not going to
设计的区域不会
be legible so I like to make sure I not
清晰易读，所以我想确保我不会
I'm not using too much of the texture
我没有用太多的纹理
over the design maybe something subtle
在设计上也许有一些微妙的东西
like that now I'll click and drag over
就这样，现在我会点击并拖动
both of those bring the opacity all the
这两者都带来了所有的不透明性
way up and go to object mask set and
向上并转到对象面罩设置，
there you go I'd say that looks pretty
就这样，我想说看起来很漂亮
good so I think that should do it for
很好，所以我认为这应该就够了
this tutorial that's how you can go
这个教程就是你可以如何去
about creating a vintage style text
关于创建复古风格文本
poster using Inkscape if you have any
如果您有，使用Inkscape的海报
questions let me know and as always
问题让我知道，一如既往
thanks for watching
感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]